<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BGIN</title>
    <link>https://bgin-global.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BGIN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bgin-global.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bgin-global.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bgin-global.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain Governance Initiative Network (BGIN) aims at providing an open and neutral sphere for all stakeholders to deepen common understanding and to collaborate to address issues they face in order to attain sustainable development of the blockchain community. As an open network, we are now actively and widely seeking interested parties to join this initiative, so as to accommodate diverse opinions from a wider range of blockchain stakeholders. For those who are interested, please start contribution at the BGIN&amp;rsquo;s GitHub repository or contact us via bgin-contact@bgin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Contributions</title>
      <link>https://bgin-global.org/contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bgin-global.org/contributions/</guid>
      <description>We are developing the Genesis Documents and Terms of Reference of BGIN to lay a solid foundation for the sustainable development of the platform. The draft was created on the launch of BGIN and is now open to public at our GitHub repository. We are seeking comments and views on these documents from anyone who has interests on this initiative.
Please refer to the press annoucement of the launch, the presentation describing about it or Inaugural Meeting Minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documents</title>
      <link>https://bgin-global.org/event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bgin-global.org/event/</guid>
      <description>BGIN online meeting [13:00-15:00 UTC, June 18, 2020] BGIN online meeting will be held on 13:00-15:00 UTC, June 18, 2020.
This is BGIN’s first public meeting where we will discuss key issues including the draft ToR of Governance Working Group and Identity &amp;amp; Privacy Enhancement Study Group, and strategies to develop the community base of BGIN. If you want to join the discussion, please fill in the registration form and submit by June 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documents</title>
      <link>https://bgin-global.org/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bgin-global.org/publications/</guid>
      <description>Finalized Documents  BGIN Declaration [March 10, 2020]  Work-in-Progress Documents   BGIN Genesis Document
  BGIN Terms of Reference(ToR)
  Governance working group initial draft ToR
  Identity/Privacy/Key management study group initial draft ToR
    *All BGIN documents can be found at our GitHub repository and active contributions are welcomed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documents</title>
      <link>https://bgin-global.org/wg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bgin-global.org/wg/</guid>
      <description>Governance Working Group  Co-Chairs: Aaron Wright(Cardozo Law School), Shigeya Suzuki(BSafe.network / Keio University / WIDE Project / BASE alliance) The Governance WG aims at developing the governance mechanism of BGIN itself. It will discuss a variety of topics including its organization structure, IPR policy and fundraising policy. Initial draft ToR of the WG will be discussed at the online meeting at June 18 New mailing list for the WG will be created soon after the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://bgin-global.org/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bgin-global.org/news/</guid>
      <description>June 2 2020   BGIN online meeting will be held on June 18, 13:00-15:00 UTC
 This is BGIN&amp;rsquo;s first public meeting where we will discuss key issues including:  draft ToR of Governance Working Group draft ToR of Identity/Privacy/Key management Study Group strategy to develop the community base of BGIN   Anyone can join the discussion. Check here for further details and online registration     March 20 2020  Creation of BGIN Github repository   March 10 2020  Declaration of the establishment of BGIN at BG2C Special Online Panel Discussion   March 9 2020  BGIN Inaugural Meeting  Meeting minutes Press release    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>